artistry and it's great fun and that
you can like maybe you maybe not
can go a long way with what you can
certainly still as We have always seen
up to Krister Linda after the dark vi
was in a swing where also toured
with after the dark which was very
fun, but then you always have them with you
have changed so much since Drag Race
and you became like Elektra I think
when you come out, it's complete
suddenly a celebrity who comes m Yes but
it's fun. There are many who are
people recognize you when you are not
Elektra Yes it has always been We have
maybe I only want it on serum I am
a serum I love serum However, not
it's my best m M eh and it is
also model or Vie effect Yes eh
well used so that smart end veren Okay
This you like what what do they do here then
Eh bioeffect these this little duo